Shayne Chang

Junior Front-End developer, have 2+ years experience in Vue, Flutter application development. Familiar with developing maintainable code.

Willing to learn, take challenges, continuously try to grow my skills and improve myself to a better level.

Outside of work, I'm a traveler, board-game-lover and a cat owner.

? Taipei, Taiwan



<u>shaynec.0205@gmail.com</u>

+886-975769025

Work Experience

December 2020 - Present

Software Developer Zencher.co

- Build APP, Web using Flutter, Vue-cli or Swift.
- Teach kids programing using swift playgrounds.
- Basic data processing by python, SQL.

FEB 2020 - DEC 2020

Bar Manager 23 Comedy, 23 Public

- Setup S.O.P. for the bar and training employees.
- Managing schedule and planing events.

MAY 2017 - DEC 2019

Owner, Partner Franchise bauble tea shop in Taipei x 3

- Setup S.O.P. for the shop.
- Hiring and training employees.
- All 3 shop were in the top 10 sales of that brand in Taiwan.

APR 2016 - APR 2017

CPO Citi bank Taiwan

- Processing trade and handling customer's requirements.
- 1st rank score during my training batch.

JAN 2013 - SEP 2014

Project Assistant Chang Gung Memorial Hospital

- Handling a project of donation AED to whole Taiwan.
- Scheduling training schedule between Drs & organization, planing business trip and events to promote AED. Writing final report.

Education

2008 - 2012

National Formosa University Multi-Media Design

Skills

Programming		Others	Languages
Swift	Bootstrap	Figma	Mandarin Chinese
Vue	PySpark	Google Sheet/Doc	English
Flutter	SQL	MS Office Word/Excel	